youadlist.com 2013-04-05

# Simple Classified Ads - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We at SimpleClassifiedAds.com knows the importance of information privacy and we value your privacy seriously. 

## Public Information Submitted by Members

SimpleClassifiedAds.com is a classified ads website which allows anyone to post their own classified ad. In order to do this, we need our members to signup by submitting their email address, user name and password. Of the three, the only information we show publicly is the user name.

When posting an ad, all information in it is shown publicly. Our members are given a choice to show their personal information such as email address, contact numbers, address, etc.

## Other Information Collected by SimpleClassifiedAds.com

Every web server gathers access logs whenever they are visited by a user. Some of the information in these access logs are kept by web servers to produce statistics page. These statistics are then used by webmasters to enhance their website and to get an overall picture of how their website is working with their visitors. Typically, the logs kept by these web servers are ip address, the page you visit, date and time of your visit, the entry link from where you entered our site and the type of browser and OS you are using. These logs are normally kept for only two weeks and is immediately discarded. Here's a sample of what's logged for one page view:

/index.php  
Http Code: 200 Date: Nov 11 00:41:03 Http Version: HTTP/1.1 Size in Bytes: 21917   
Referer: http://www.techcraze.net/   
Agent: Mozilla/5.0 (Windows; U; Windows NT 5.1; en-US; rv:1.8.1) Gecko/20061010 Firefox/2.0 

Log data may be examined by our developers in the course of solving technical problems and in tracking down badly-behaved web spiders or users that overwhelm the site.

## Third Party Advertising Companies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## **Release of Data**

The only time we would be releasing data collected from our server logs is on the following cases:

  * Cumpulsory request or subpoena from law enforcement agency.
  * When information needs to be dissected to resolve technical issues. 
  * When data needs to be released to assist in blocking of IP blocks or to formulate a compalin to a relevant Internet Service Provider. 
  * When it is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of SimpleClassifiedAds.com and its users.

We do not release these information for any other reasons except those above. 

## Security

SimpleClassifiedAds.com makes no guarantee against unauthorized access or hacks to any information you provide. We are making all the efforts to ensure the security of this Web site and we take every precaution to protect the information of our members, as well as information collected from other users of the SimpleClassifiedAds.com website. We limit the access to this information only to those employees who need access to perform their job function. However, we do not guarantee against any unauthorized access or hacks to any information you provide. 

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy anytime we deem necessary. We will post changes here so members and other users of the SimpleClassifiedAds.com are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use members' or other users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify those members and users by placing a prominent notice on our website.
